{
    "concepts_list": [
        "Computer Knowledge",
        "Data Representation",
        "Modules",
        "Data Handling",
        "Data Types",
        "Syntax Knowledge",
        "List Methods"
    ],
    "questions_list": [
        {
            "type": "MCQ",
            "level": "EASY",
            "concepts": [
                "Computer Knowledge"
            ],
            "question": "Which type of language is Python?",
            "options": [
                "Compiled",
                "Interpreted",
                "Assembled",
                "Executed"
            ],
            "correct_option": "Interpreted",
            "hash": "MEeWCtdEr"
        },
        {
            "type": "MCQ",
            "level": "EASY",
            "concepts": [
                "Data Representation"
            ],
            "question": "What is the base of decimal number system?",
            "options": [
                "2",
                "8",
                "10",
                "16"
            ],
            "correct_option": "10",
            "hash": "MEph28110"
        },
        {
            "type": "MCQ",
            "level": "EASY",
            "concepts": [
                "Data Representation"
            ],
            "question": "What is the base of octal number system?",
            "options": [
                "2",
                "8",
                "10",
                "16"
            ],
            "correct_option": "8",
            "hash": "MEai28118"
        },
        {
            "type": "MCQ",
            "level": "EASY",
            "concepts": [
                "Data Representation"
            ],
            "question": "What is the base of hexadecimal number system?",
            "options": [
                "2",
                "8",
                "10",
                "16"
            ],
            "correct_option": "16",
            "hash": "MEe_28111"
        },
        {
            "type": "MCQ",
            "level": "EASY",
            "concepts": [
                "Data Representation"
            ],
            "question": "Which of the following is not a possible base for a number system?",
            "options": [
                "1",
                "2",
                "3",
                "4"
            ],
            "correct_option": "1",
            "hash": "MErh12341"
        },
        {
            "type": "MCQ",
            "level": "EASY",
            "concepts": [
                "Data Representation"
            ],
            "question": "How many digits in base-n number system?",
            "options": [
                "n",
                "n+1",
                "n-1",
                "10-n"
            ],
            "correct_option": "n",
            "hash": "MEp_n11-n"
        },
        {
            "type": "MCQ",
            "level": "EASY",
            "concepts": [
                "Modules"
            ],
            "question": "Which module can be used to calculate mean of a data set?",
            "options": [
                "statistics",
                "math",
                "random",
                "average"
            ],
            "correct_option": "statistics",
            "hash": "MEohatnet"
        },
        {
            "type": "MCQ",
            "level": "EASY",
            "concepts": [
                "Data Handling"
            ],
            "question": "Which method is used to add an item to the end of a list in Python?",
            "options": [
                "append()",
                "add()",
                "insert()",
                "addend()"
            ],
            "correct_option": "append()",
            "hash": "MEdeaaiap"
        },
        {
            "type": "MCQ",
            "level": "MEDIUM",
            "concepts": [
                "Modules",
                "Data Types"
            ],
            "question": "Which of the following is not immutable?",
            "options": [
                "tuple",
                "string",
                "int",
                "list"
            ],
            "correct_option": "list",
            "hash": "MMeTcprtss"
        },
        {
            "type": "MCQ",
            "level": "EASY",
            "concepts": [
                "Modules",
                "Syntax Knowledge"
            ],
            "question": "Which of the following is used to create a list?",
            "options": [
                "[]",
                "{}",
                "()",
                "<>"
            ],
            "correct_option": "[]",
            "hash": "MEexc[{(<["
        },
        {
            "type": "MCQ",
            "level": "EASY",
            "concepts": [
                "Syntax Knowledge",
                "List Methods"
            ],
            "question": "Which method is used to remove an element from a list by value?",
            "options": [
                "remove()",
                "pop()",
                "del",
                "discard()"
            ],
            "correct_option": "remove()",
            "hash": "MEyih(odde"
        }
    ]
}